[MILITARY POLICE 82A]
Found a survivor! Over here!
Come give me a hand!
[MILITARY POLICE 82B]
Keep it steady!
We'll get you to safety.
Everything's gonna
be okay, ma'am.
[PARADIS MAN 82A] The Titans of
the walls started marching
away from the island in ranks.
[PARADIS MAN 82B]
It definitely doesn't seem like
they were targeting us,
but even so.
Can't get it out of my head.
That daydream that came
when the walls fell.
[PARADIS WOMAN 82A]
My home.
Eren Jaeger took
my home from me.
Everything's gone.
[PARADIS MAN 82A] A few houses
are a small price to pay.
[PARADIS MAN 82B]
How dare you say that?
[PARADIS MAN 82C]
This man just lost his son!
Who knows how many people died
when the walls came down?
[PARADIS MAN 82D] They didn't
just "die." Eren killed them!
That's a plain fact.
You can blame Eren Jaeger for
everyone we lost
when the walls fell.
But we know what
would have happened
to those people if the Titans
hadn't been awakened.
The invaders would have
exterminated them
along with everyone
else on the island!
[PARADIS MAN 82E] That's right!
Eldian blood was spilled today
so that the Eldian
Empire could live on!
That's the price of victory!
[PARADIS MAN 82A] None of
our people died in vain!
Honor their sacrifice!
Give your hearts!
[PARADIS MEN] Give your hearts!
--Hey, Hitch?
--Yeah, this is bad.
With things as heated
as they are,
we could get mobs of civilians
clashing in the streets.
Then we should probably
quip ourselves accordingly.
Grab as much riot gear as you
can pile onto these carts!
[RECRUITS]
Understood!
[HITCH] What are those lunatics
in Shiganshina up to?
[HITCH]
They came from the basement?
[ANNIE] You make a sound,
I slit your throat.
[ANNIE]
Take off the jacket, slowly.
You're so weak,
it felt like someone's granny
had gotten me in a chokehold.
Who'd have thought
the day would come
when I'd be the one tossing
you around, eh, Annie?
Hitch, of all people?
Seriously? What a joke.
[HITCH]
This could get bad real quick.
I gotta get her in the basement.
Somebody help!
[ANNIE]
Too late.
[Gasps]
I already opened myself up.
I'll transform
if you give me a reason.
If you wanna live,
you'll have to do what I say.
Now, get off me.
I don't think I will.
If you can't take me in a fight,
there's no way you have
the energy to go Titan.
[ANNIE]
Maybe you're right about that.
Only one way to
find out though, right?
[RECRUIT 82A]
Is everything okay, Dreyse?
[Gasps]
[knocking]
[RECRUIT 82A]
Dreyse? Can you hear me?
[knocking]
[RECRUIT 82A]
I'm coming in!
♪ Opening Song ♪
[ANNIE]
Looks like you're smarter
than I gave you credit for.
[HITCH]
Shut up. If you wanna skip town,
I've got no reason
to stand in your way.
Matter of fact, it's nice
to imagine not having to
see your face or
that basement ever again.
Then I'm happy for you, Hitch.
And for what it's worth,
the feeling is mutual.
It was torture,
having to hear you
whine about your
crap taste in men.
[HITCH gasps] How could you
know what I was saying?
No way. Were you...
conscious that whole time?
Four long years.
It was like some hazy dream
that wouldn't end.
[ANNIE] When you and Armin were
there in the basement,
I could hear you talking,
off in the distance.
And when you weren't,
there was nothing.
Except me and the darkness.
[ANNIE]
Thanks to you,
I was pretty much
able to keep up with
everything that was going on
in the outside world.
And then, my hardening
came undone,
and I was on the floor,
hearing Eren's voice in my head.
Is he seriously
doing what he said?
Crushing the whole world flat?
The Titans of the Walls
really are on the march.
[HITCH] Now, look what's
down at their feet.
[HITCH] The only meaningful work
I've done as a soldier
is prying rubble off people
and gathering corpses.
Cleaning up after you and Eren.
[HITCH]
Can I finally get an answer?
Seeing all those
lifeless bodies,
crushed in the name
of some grand plan
they never knew about.
How does it feel?
[ANNIE]
Yeah. You've asked that a lot,
and I've thought about it.
About how little we'd
thought about it before.
All we were ever praised for
was how good we were at killing.
[ANNIE] Outside Marley's
borders, we were taught
not to distinguish between
soldiers and civilians.
They were all just the enemy.
We were atoning for the
sins of the Eldian people
and working towards the goal
of saving the world.
No matter who we had to kill,
we were justified.
[HITCH]
Armin already told me about
the situation you were in.
I get it. This is what
you wanted to prevent.
And a few hundred
thousand innocent lives
is a small price to pay
to save the world, right?
[ANNIE]
No. I never really gave a damn
about saving the world.
It didn't matter to me.
The world wasn't worth saving.
Not in my eyes.
My parents abandoned me
when I was born.
[ANNIE] I was the product
of my mother's affair
with an Eldian man.
They left me inside the gates
of the internment zone.
A foreigner with Eldian blood
found me there and took me in.
[ANNIE] He and I had similar
stories and we
ended up in the same place.
[ANNIE]
But that's not why he did it.
He wanted to mold me into
one of Marley's Warriors.
Use me as his ticket
to a better life.
[ANNIE]
Even in my earliest memories,
that man was already
beating the martial arts
of his homeland into me.
That was my only value to him.
He said that becoming a Warrior
was the reason I was given life.
[ANNIE]
As I grew up,
I got stronger,
just like he'd hoped I would.
And I paid him back
for all the pain
he'd caused me in the process.
[ANNIE] I gave him a limp
that'll stay with him
for the rest of his life.
And yet, I'd never
seen him look happier.
"Now I know you
can kill," he said.
"Even unarmed."
[HITCH] Okay, wait. I don't need
to hear your entire life story.
[ANNIE] I didn't need to hear
about every failed relationship
you've had in
the past four years.
It's not gonna kill you to let
me talk for a few minutes.
Anyway, the point is.
Nothing mattered to me.
I didn't care about
the people I fought with,
or those we fought.
I didn't see the value in any
human life, including my own.
[ANNIE]
Until that day.
The morning we set out,
he fell to his knees
and started apologizing.
He said he didn't
expect me to forgive him.
And then,
through tears, he said:
"Promise me you'll return."
He didn't care about
securing his place
as an Honorary Marleyan.
He just wanted to know
that I'd make it back.
[ANNIE]
In that moment,
I knew that we
really were family.
That when he looked at me,
he saw his daughter.
[ANNIE]
So, now.
I have a father waiting
for me to come home.
[ANNIE] And I realize
that everyone has people
who are just as important
to them, as he is to me.
I can't just tell myself
nothing matters anymore.
It all matters.
And after what I've done,
I don't think I can
ever be redeemed.
[ANNIE]
But...
If it would get me back to
my dad, I'd do it all again.
Thank you. I'm glad you
shared that with me.
But I'm sorry.
I don't think you'll have
anything to go back to now
but a corpse in the rubble.
[ANNIE]
I know.
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Sir, please,
I couldn't make this up!
You had that
daydream too, right?
This was inevitable.
Those island devils
were always going to be
the death of us in the end.
Please be okay, Gabi.
[COLT'S MOTHER]
Oh, Falco.
As we speak, the rumbling
has already begun!
Eren Jaeger is on his way
with an army of Titans
to kill everyone here!
Your home and family
and everything you care for
is about to be stomped flat!
[Gasps] You really
expect me to believe
a word out of your
hell-spawn mouths?
You all had the
same dream, and what,
you think we'll just
let you through the gate?
You're putting on
a show, aren't you?
How long have you swine
been planning this?
If you call up
any internment zone
in the whole world right now,
every Eldian will be
saying the same thing!
Do you honestly think we all
could've coordinated
that somehow?
And how do I know
that you didn't?
As a matter of fact,
this is beginning to
feel like an admission
of conspiracy!
Round 'em all up!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 82B]
Get on your knees!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 82C]
Hands behind your heads!
He said,
"Hands behind your head!"
[ANNIE'S FATHER]
Promise me you'll return.
That's all I ask.
[ANNIE]
Okay. I promise, Dad.
[Yells]
Gunfire?
[SURMA]
I've got bad news.
The Jaegerists are
taking over the fort.
If they catch you,
who knows what they'll do?
You should run for it before
they find out you're here, sir.
It's fine.
There isn't any place
for me to go at this point.
The core of our
military is gone,
literally sliced at the nape.
The Jaegerists are
gaining popular support.
They're securing
the island as we speak.
That means finishing off
the old regime.
They're gonna want me dead.
And I'm too old for exile.
I don't wanna
have to shit outdoors
on some lonely mountain.
We'd've been eaten alive
if not for you, sir.
We won't leave you now!
That's right,
no matter what happens next,
we'll fight to keep you safe!
[KEITH]
You damn fools.
[BOTH gasp]
[KEITH] Why do you think I
rolled over and let a bunch of
wimpy tots like you pretend you
had the grit to kick my ass?
[BOTH gasp]
[KEITH]
Keep your heads down.
Do exactly as
the Jaegerists say.
All that you punks can
protect is yourselves.
So focus on that.
Go out and toe
the Jaegerist line.
That's the only way?
[KEITH]
It is.
Live long enough and you'll
get your chance to rebel.
In the meantime, do your best
not to lose yourselves.
[MIKASA]
Armin. Wait.
Connie has too much
of a lead now.
You won't reach Ragako in time.
And besides.
There's nothing you could say
if you did catch him.
You really plan to ask him
to give up on saving his mother?
You think that's right?
Yeah, I do.
And even if I am bound to fail,
I still have to do everything
I possibly can to save Falco.
Because if I don't, then Gabi
will never come to trust us.
It's crucial that
we win her over.
Reiner and the Cart Titan are
still out there somewhere
and I believe she's
the best hope we have
of creating some kind
of truce with them.
It's not as if the issue
of Titan inheritance
is going away anytime soon.
If worse comes to worse,
we could end up
in another struggle
for control of the Nine.
Repeating the wars of
the last two thousand years,
but on this tiny
little island of ours.
[ARMIN]
Honestly, I'm so exhausted,
all I wanna do is sleep
for the next couple days.
But human history is passing
through a bottleneck right now,
so the actions we choose to take
could have a huge
impact on the future.
He can't go through with this.
So yeah, I'll tell
Conny that his mom
might need to stay
a Titan forever.
See you later.
[MIKASA] Armin.
Any idea what I should do?
Seems likely that
Jean could use your help.
You'll have to figure out
the rest for yourself.
[MIKASA]
So what'll we do about Eren?
[ARMIN]
How the hell should I know?
Who says there's
anything we can do?
Not only are Hange
and the Captain
probably dead right now,
but if we get on
Floch's bad side,
we might get to join them.
Let's see what else.
Oh right, Annie's
probably back in action.
And what's left
of the military's
chain of command
has been shattered.
It's in chaos!
Also. Historia's probably
in danger right now.
Along with the
Azumabito clan, Nicolo,
and the Volunteers from Marley.
It's too much!
There's no point
in worrying about Eren,
we can't stop him,
he's a lost cause!
Why can't you understand that?
[Gasps]
[MIKASA]
Sorry.
[ARMIN] If you were talking to
Commander Erwin right now,
there's no way he would've
snapped at you like that.
I guess we know for a fact now.
Captain Levi saved
the wrong person.
He should've chosen Erwin.
[MIKASA]
My scarf, it's gone.
[ARTUR]
Conny's a decent sort.
Even if it's for
his mother's sake.
He won't be able to sacrifice
a kid's life just like that.
I'm sure he'll hesitate.
You should make it in time.
[GABI]
Thank you, Mr. Braus.
Think I'm gonna stick with them.
I'll do my best to
get them out of here.
My advice is to get as deep into
the countryside
as you can, then.
[KAYA]
Mia.
Take care, okay?
My name isn't actually
Mia, you know.
It's Gabi. Gabi Braun.
Huh? That sounds so weird.
Bet you wish your name was Mia.
Huh?
[GABI]
See you, Kaya.
[KAYA]
Goodbye, Gabi.
Put the gun down, Floch.
Don't kill him!
I wasn't planning to.
I'm just helping him wake up.
He didn't seem to comprehend
the situation he was in,
but I think I've
gotten message across.
Now these volunteers
know what'll happen
if they're mouthy
or make trouble.
Hey. Last I checked,
this island didn't have a king,
so who the hell
nominated you to act like one?
[FLOCH]
I'm so glad you asked, Jean.
All right, people, listen up!
Ten months back,
I talked to Eren.
And he told me all about
his plan to protect Eldia.
He laid out every detail,
right up to the moment
we all witnessed,
when he used Founder's power!
[Gasps]
He said to gather up comrades.
I did, and with our help,
he's been able to secure
our island's future!
You volunteers have
lost your leader,
and thanks to your wine,
the old military isn't here
to back you, either.
What's more, you're about
to lose your homelands!
The whole world will soon be
flattened in great,
smoldering footprints.
Whatever chance
you thought you had
of liberating your peoples
and reviving your countries,
you can give up on it now!
You're beaten,
but if any of you would like
to set the past aside
and serve Eldia
for its own sake,
now's the time to speak.
Join us and we'll welcome you as
full citizens of the
new Eldian Empire!
Who the hell do you think
you are? I'll die before--
[FLOCH]
Pay your respects!
[FLOCH] This man kept
his pride to the end.
He refused to submit
no matter what.
To him, dignity was
worth dying for.
But if you're asking my opinion,
you should just give in.
Is submitting really worse
than ending up like this?
[FLOCH] Take some time to
think it over. Lock 'em up.
[JAEGERIST 82A]
Yes, sir!
Wait, what's going on here?
Jean. What just happened?
[FLOCH]
To answer your question,
I'm taking action
on Eren's behalf.
He has his hands
full solving problems
outside of the island right now,
so I'm wiping out whatever
resentment is left within it.
Four years ago, all of us
went through hell.
But now, after suffering
through so much,
we've finally earned our reward.
Can you still
not see it yourself?
You're finally free.
You don't have any
obligation to fight anymore.
You can live as
you please now, Jean.
[FLOCH]
It's okay.
You wanted to live the good life
in the interior as an MP right?
Then go do it.
You're one of Eldia's heroes.
I don't have to fight?
No, you don't.
You can simply go back
to being the old Jean.
Be as annoying, selfish,
and arrogant as you please.
Well that's kinda rude.
[Gasp]
Tell me, Floch.
Do you know what happened to
Captain Levi and
Commander Hange?
[FLOCH] Ah. Unfortunately,
they were killed by Zeke.
[FALCO] Conny. I appreciate
your helping me, but um,
aren't we still going north?
I mean look.
The sun's setting over there.
That's for the best.
We need to get as from the south
as we can, it's dangerous.
With any luck,
the hospital I'm taking you to
will be able to
treat your amnesia.
I found you all by yourself,
collapsed on the ground.
It's true, all right?
I'm a soldier,
so it's only natural
that I would do what I could.
[CONNY] That's right.
I've become a soldier.
[CONNY'S MOTHER] Become a
great soldier, okay, Connie?
You'll be everyone's protector!
[CONNY]
Dad, Sunny, and Martin are gone.
They're never coming back.
But Mom still has a chance.
Just wait a little
bit longer, Mom.
I've become a soldier. And now--
[FALCO]
Thanks so much, Conny.
You've really gone
out of your way for me.
I'm grateful.
[CONNY]
It's nothing.
[FALCO] I'm lucky I was
found by such a good person,
but I need to get back
south somehow.
I remember everything up to
when I met Colt and Gabi,
but everything
after that is a blur.
[FALCO]
Also. This Conny guy.
I feel like I've seen him
somewhere before.
Still, if he doesn't know me,
then maybe that's
just my imagination.
[PIECK] Judging from
their speed and heading,
it seems likely
that the airships
are withdrawing to Marley.
I guess once they saw
the rumbling start,
they panicked and decided
to save themselves,
leaving the rest of us for dead.
[MAGATH]
No. They did the right thing.
Our forces in Marley need to
be informed as
quickly as possible.
If the ships had
waited for stragglers,
they might've been crushed.
Fair, but even with warning,
what'll our forces
be able to do?
Is there any real hope?
Can these Titans be stopped?
No. But still,
we'll struggle against
the inevitable for
as long as we can.
[HANGE]
Excuse me.
[BOTH gasp]
[HANGE]
Whoa, whoa, wait!
No need to eat me, okay?
I'm not a threat, I didn't
even bring any weapons.
Oh! Wondering who
I've got over there?
Yeah. He's not a
threat either, honest.
He's just a poor bastard
who refuses to die.
[NARRATOR] The walls of
Paradis continue to walk.
When the people
of the world look up
and see their colossal figures,
will they be frozen with fear?
Or will they strike back?
Next episode: "Pride."